Good evening everyone. We are the morning team. Us,
We are A.B. Junior High School.
Attendance number 16, Ayama Sakurai,
Attendance number 17, Yuna Nakamura.
Yes, we are.
Before we start the program, we would like to choose today's MC.
Please vote for your favorite one, 1 or 2, since we are holding the numbered cards.
The person who has the number card with the number on it is today's MC.
So let's start voting.
All right.
Yuna, it's been a while since you were here.
It's been since September. Last year.
September?
September. Already 3 or 6.
It's been almost a year. That's for sure. It's not good. September. It's been 3, 6, and September.
It's been almost a year.
That's for sure.
It's been almost a year. And who did you do it with last time?
Last time was in the mountains, and the time before that, and the time before that, with Nonoka, and the time before that, in the mountains.
You know, you can only go out with me.
That's all there is to it. Is that okay?
Okay.
Okay, five, four, three, two, one.
Ding.
Yes, and the result is...
Whoa!
Big Sada is so big!
Yes, indeed.
Number 2.
Number two.
Okay.
Yes, sir.
Ha!
So today's MC is Nakamura. I look forward to working with you.
Okay, I'll take over the MC baton here.
Yes, I'm Nakamura.
I'm looking forward to working with you. Please do.
Let's begin.
Ebichu's Funny and Fufu SHOWROOM
What a surprise, today is our 70th episode.
Thank you for watching EBITCHU'S FUFU FUFU FUFU FUFU FUFU FUFU FUFU FUFU FUFU SHOWROOM.
Ebichu's Funny and Fufufu SHOWROOM is,
It is the sister show of our sister show, Uka-san's SHOWROOM.
Yes, I know, I know, I know.
So, this is the time to spread the word.
I hope that as many people as possible will watch this distribution,
I'm going to announce it on the official Ebichu X page now,
Please spread the word, everyone.
Thank you very much.
Please spread the word.
It will be announced on the official X page of Ebichu now,
So, that's it,
Oh, here it is. It's important.
I'll ring it for nothing.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Today I would like to do a project like this.
It's called "Delightful Marital Survey Talk!"
Yay! It's called "Hilarious Married Couple Survey Talk!"
Yay!
Before the talk, we will take a questionnaire to decide the content of the talk. That is the Questionnaire Talk.
First of all, I'll make an announcement before taking the survey.
Ta-da!
Hee!
(1) 15th Anniversary Tour Hokkaido & Aichi & Ibaraki & Tokyo
Yay!
2) Taipei soon!
Taipei
(3) Honorary Prawn Ambassador
Ebi Ambassador
4) Yuna Nakamura's Birthday Solo Live
Phew!
5) Conquer 0000 5) Overcome 0000
6) Happy Birthday, Yasumoto-san!
Happy Birthday
7) Emayuna Enoshima
So we have two amazing people, but they have funky hair color...yes Mr. Yasumoto, Happy Birthday! Happy Birthday!07, Emayuna Enoshima!
So we have two amazing people, though,
Funky hair color.
We have a survey coming from one of these.
Please choose one.
Go ahead!
Start!
What's what?
But there's so many.
I knew he's here.
I'm sure.
I'd like to hear about it. It's already been a month.
It's already been a month. That was fast.
Time flies, doesn't it?
Indeed.
What's left?
I'm still interested in overcoming 0000.
Five, four, three, two, one.
That's too loud.
There's too many 7s.
Emayuna Enoshima.
Okay, let's talk about this.
What a surprise we got to go out in our uniforms, which we have always wanted to do.
Thank you very much.
It was really our wish to go out in Emayuna,
I knew it for a long time.
But I think there are some people who know a lot about it,
But, as some of you may know, there was the Asakusa Incident,
It was difficult for the two of us to go out together,
That's right.
We couldn't, but it started with the fact that we wanted to wear uniforms,
I said, "Let's wear sailors to Enoshima,
We both found one and bought matching sailors,
We bought matching sailors. We had a great time, and the pictures were great! I bought one, too. The pictures were great!
I posted them on Instagram, and everyone saw them.
It was really a youthful time, and we had a lot of fun,
It was delicious.
It was delicious. It was really delicious.
It was amazing.
It was really good. I had never been to Enoshima.
It was my first time to eat seafood in Kanagawa, and it was really good. The baby sardines.
It was delicious.
It was delicious. And then I had an acai ball.
I continued with my staple food, and I had an acai ball. I continued with my staple food staple food, and I ate an acai ball.
Yes, I ate it.
After that, I went to Kamakura and ate,
I ate all the time.
I ate crepes.
I ate crepes. They were delicious.
We ate crepes and drank Ramune,
Yeah, yeah.
We ended up at Tully's for some reason.
That's right.
Tully's was the place to end the party. We didn't have enough to finish.
I don't know why,
I had Yuna's first assignment.
Yes, I had only had a fake assignment,
I had never had a proper asain ball before, but it was so delicious.
I had never had a proper Assign Ball before, but it was really tasty.
I thought it was a kind of healthy food,
I thought it would be something healthy, so I didn't think I would want to eat it so much,
I thought it would be something healthy, so I thought it wouldn't make me want to eat it so much, but it did.
It was delicious.
Nothing happened?
Did anything happen?
Yes, but we both got really sleepy on the way there.
Yeah.
Yes, it did.
At the crepe shop,
Right, at the crepe shop. At the crepe shop. Yes, at the crepe shop. Right, isn't it a crepe shop? A crepe shop, yes, a crepe shop, yes, a crepe shop.
Even at a crepe shop,
I was eating something, well, laminated,
I suddenly had a sleeping spell,
I fell asleep.
I slept while eating crepes.
I fell asleep while eating a crepe.
He was talking to me about something now, and all I could say was, "Oh, I see,
I thought he must have been sleepy.
I was sleepy at the time, and even on the train I was a little sleepy,
So we ended up at Tully's and broke up in a very low state of tension.
That was terrible.
Tully's. Why did we go to Tully's?
Well, I don't know,
I don't know why we went there,
But I went there.
I went in there. Why? The closing.
Why?
I fell asleep eating a crepe. See, see.
But they were delicious. Sugar butter.
Hey! It was delicious.
When I was little, I used to like chocolate bananas.
But I really enjoyed the simple taste of sugar butter.
It's really good. I want you all to try it.
You must be tired from walking, that's for sure.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's part of it, too.
Please, everyone, please go there.
Please go.
Next time, let's go to Asakusa.
Yes, let's go to Asakusa.
Let's go to Asakusa. That's right. Asakusa.
Some of you may not know this,
It's the case that I was cancelled the day before Asakusa.
I'm sorry.
I was told to do a report.
I see.
Then definitely, I would like to go to Asakusa next time. Then definitely, I would like to go to Asakusa next time.
I would like to go there.
Shall we go?
Would you like to take a survey this time?
Yes.
Okay, let's do it. The survey is about to start. Then, do you want to go to Sayanke?
I did the survey.
I'm not 7, it's just the four of them.
It seems to be the four of them, and Kyoto, too.
I want to go today!
What?
Five, four, three, two, one.
Okay, here we go. Here it comes!
Number 4!
It's number 4, hands down.
Yuna Nakamura's birthday surprise.
She asked me to tell you about it.
Well, well, you know, it was already a month ago, so I don't remember many details,
Well, it was fun, wasn't it?
That's right.
It was fun. It was my own idea of an astry, so it was fun,
The costumes were cute, too.
It was cute. It was white, pure white.
I wanted to make it pure white.
It was kind of mature.
Really?
Yes, it was.
Last time, it was light blue and pink,
I felt like I shouldn't call it cute,
This time it was girly, but a little white and mature.
Thank you very much.
It was really good.
The last song of the show was quite mature,
That's for sure.
The lighting was glittery, so we matched it,
It was really good. We went with the white glittery type.
It was great.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
Setley did a great job.
Did you decide on the medley yourself, from here to here and from here to here for this song?
Yes, I wrote everything down. I wrote it all down,
I started with the evidences week,
There is no place to cut between evidences, is there?
That's true. All the time.
It was like a schedule, and there was no part that could be cut,
So we had to think about how to use one song, or how to use one part of a song because it was good,
I thought about it and made it myself,
I practiced.
It was amazing.
I said, "Twenty minutes is too much.
Was it 20 minutes?
Sure, but that's how long it took.
We packed it in.
It was my "Ebi Mani" of the moment,
I had never done that before.
I had never done it before.
Basically, you had never played it before either.
That's right.
Old songs.
Yeah, yeah.
I was surprised to find that there are some recent songs that are not included in the six members' repertoire,
I'm going to talk about something that has nothing to do with me.
I found a song by 10 members that is a bit weird.
What is it?
Hamidase Girls.
Weird song? Yes, it is. I see. Is it "Ha"? Hamidase Girls.
Weird song?
Yes, it is.
I see.
We did "Hagidashi Girls" and "Ishi ni Iri" too,
I thought it was a theme that I had never done before,
So I decided not to do it,
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes. Yes, yes, yes.
But it was great fun.
The medley, you know, I was happy to hear cheers all the way.
Yes, it was.
Because, you know, it made me go "ah-ha!
It made you say, "Yes, yes!
Emma was cheering, too.
Emma got it? Really?
Emma loves sweets stavok too much,
Really? I'm so happy.
I'm so glad.
I was free. We did it.
I want to do Sweets Stabok, too.
I want to do that. I've never done it before. I've never done it in junior.
I love Bongolee too much.
So, Emma loves bongolee?
I love bongolee too much. So, Emma is a bongolee? I didn't have bongolee, but sure.
Emma told me she didn't realize she was a photographer.
Emma and Yuna.
But that was also done on short notice.
At first, Yuna came back for the second encore song,
I was waiting for Yuna to come back to the end of the show to say good night,
I was waiting for her to say good night and then I asked her if she wanted to take a picture with the camera. I was waiting for her to say good night and send her off, but she asked me if I wanted to take her camera,
I said, "Is it OK? I said, "Oh, you don't mind?
Yuna-chan and Yuna wanted to go too,
When Yuna and Yuna wanted to go with the cameraman, the two of us went out with the cameraman,
Yuna didn't realize it yet.
I didn't notice.
I forgot to take a picture, didn't I?
I forgot.
I forgot to take a nice picture, didn't I? I forgot! I forgot to take a good picture,
And the fans kept saying, "HIRO-chan!
I was wondering why they didn't listen to me since everyone kept calling me HIRO-chan, and then they told me.
So they took a picture of me, and it was a lot of fun.
I'm glad, seriously. There was a comment earlier, you know, that said the front memory was great.
I'm so happy, so happy.
When I heard that, I was thinking about your audition, Yosobi's...
Oh, it just reminded me of the audition, Yosobi's audition. Oh, I just remembered to give you that.
Thank you. Really?
You just mentioned a different song by a different group.
That was really funny.
I'm glad.
It was really good.
It was really difficult.
Yes, it was. He said it was the most nerve-wracking.
It was the most nerve-wracking. That song was really difficult.
I was like, "Who can sing that song?
I could sing it.
So I was really nervous.
It was amazing. I'm glad.
Thank you very much. But I still want to do Ebbimanion with 10 members.
I want to do it! I want to do it with Eva, too!
I want to do it.
It looked like a lot of fun.
It looked like they were having a great time.
Get!
I'm sorry.
This one came in the show.
I had a great trauma.
I've been traumatized for a week during the shrimping.
It was great.
It was fun.
There were still many songs that I fell in love with Seto.
Bevanny.
There are many more.
There are many more songs in "Bevanny".
So, I want to do it freely.
Let's do it.
We won.
Yes, that's good.
It was fun.
Good, good, good.
One more.
Shall we have one more?
Let's start the survey. Survey started.
I knew everyone would want to see Ebimani.
I want to see it. I like it.
Let's do it.
I'm interested in the illustrations.
That's true.
They're everywhere.
It's a shrimp. A shrimp.
I can't help but notice that he's smiling.
Don't say "mechade.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Yes, I'd like to see the results.
Number five.
00 00 confession.
Who's talking? This one.
Yes.
Please.
Sakurayama00I made a confession,
What is this?
I confessed my kikurage. I overcame it, but what is this?
I have conquered kikurage.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
I have recently realized that this is how people become adults, one by one.
I didn't know you hated kikurage.
Not that I didn't like it, I just didn't like to eat it,
You often find kikurage in ramen noodles, don't you?
Yes, they do.
I eat ramen, but my mother likes it all, so I used to give it to her.
I used to wonder why she ate so much kikurage because she ate so much,
Recently, one of the younger members of the group goes to a rice cake place called Ma Lertang.
There is a topping called "white kikurage" that is available there,
It was really delicious,
It's delicious, isn't it?
It's so good, isn't it?
I was hooked after I had it,
Then I started eating regular kikurage,
It was too delicious. It was already too delicious.
I've conquered kikurage.
That thing, he said, even though I can't eat mushrooms a little right now,
He told me that kikurage is a mushroom, and I didn't know that either.
I thought it was seaweed or something,
I thought it was a mushroom.
I was so surprised.
It's like I've gotten over mushrooms.
That's true. You can't eat all mushrooms?
Only enoki mushrooms?
I can eat them.
I can.
Wow, I like shiitake mushrooms.
Hey, you don't like them?
You don't like them?
Hey.
Shiitake mushrooms.
I couldn't really sympathize with him.
Shiitake mushrooms are delicious.
Shiitake mushrooms.
Do you taste it?
I've never sought the taste of mushrooms. It's not about the texture, you know, mushrooms. Don't wood jellyfish have a taste, too?
No, they don't. That's for sure. The crunchy texture is delicious. Mushrooms are,
They don't taste like mushrooms. They're called tree jellyfish.
I don't get tree jellyfish. All I have ever tasted was jellyfish.
Jellyfish that grows into trees is called kikurage.
So, you know, today, on the news, when they said that tree jellyfish are growing on trees...
Yes, a jellyfish is growing on a tree.
When I heard that, I wondered if something unusual like that had happened, but it seemed to be normal.
I was surprised. I was surprised to see something I usually eat growing on a tree,
I was so surprised.
And when I asked him about it later, he said, "It says 'ear' on the tree,
That's right.
I didn't know that, too. I didn't know that either.
I didn't even know that.
I thought it was written in hiragana.
It reminds me of the Yokan incident.
What?Eh?
Haha, please read it.
Um, Emma looks at the kanji characters for yokan. Please read it.
Well, when Emma saw the kanji characters for yokan, she said she couldn't read them,
Well, it's not that she can't read the kanji.
It's difficult.
But yokan is usually written in katakana. But yokan is usually written in katakana. I was told, "No, it's not written in katakana,
I remember an incident in which I did not get much sympathy.
I had an image of katakana.
I have never seen yokan written in katakana.
Kanji characters have become difficult.
It is difficult. It is indeed difficult to write.
You don't see kanji anywhere, do you?
I don't see it, but it's not katakana.
I'm sorry.
I really embarrassed you all, didn't I? At that time.
Katakana? What am I mistaking it for?
I think they must have mistaken it for something. Maybe.
I wonder.
Well, that was the story. Emma overcame kikurage.
Well, I'd like to go one more. Please vote for me.
This is what Nakamura wants to talk about.
This is what Nakamura wants to talk about. Yuna Nakamura, I was able to go to Ayaka Yasumoto's birthday solo live yesterday,
It was a wonderful live performance. I saw a lot of reports about it, and Emma was very excited about it,
I really wanted to go.
It was wonderful. It was fun.
I was listening to a lot of Aya's original songs,
That was fun, too,
I also enjoyed the Bitume medley.
I see. It was like a preemptive Famie, wasn't it?
I thought it was a famie. I didn't have my towel with me,
I didn't have my towel with me, and there was a song in the medley where people were waving their towels around,
It was just me and Nonoka. I was alone.
Nonoka and I didn't have towels,
I thought about what to wave around, so I folded a paper ticket I had and enjoyed shaking it,
We enjoyed waving them around,
After that, I sang to all the members, past and present,
I was so happy to sing about my beloved one. He told me he was going to sing my darling.
Kyun!
It's Kyun, isn't it?
Kyun.
That's a Kyun, isn't it?
That's a "kyun.
I stretched my back and listened.
I wish I could have listened to it.
It was so much fun.
It was nice.
The costumes were really cute, too.
It was cute. I was like, "Are you sure you want me to look at your belly like that? It was like, "Can I look at your belly like that?
You don't mind me looking at her belly like that?
Yes. And then she came out for encore wearing a cute hat.
You know, that one?
Like a rabbit.
It was cute.
It was cute. That was cute, too.
I've made up my mind what I like about Aya,
I like her energy during the MC,
I like the way she said "Thank you very much,
I thought that students' throats get tired when they perform solo, so she says "thank you" to everyone.
I have an image of her as a whispering type, but I feel that no matter what kind of MC she does, she is always full of energy.
It was wonderful.
Thank you, thank you, thank you" soaked into my heart.
It was a heartfelt "thank you" that really touched my heart.
It was good. She had a mermaid hanging from her waist.
That was cute.
Is that a bear?
Is that a bear or a rabbit?
He was wearing a stuffed bear or rabbit,
It was amazing.
It was cute.
It was cute. It was cute.
The DJ corner was a lot of fun.
It was like there was a connection between here and there.
Oh, that's right.
Yes, it was. It was amazing. It's amazing to be able to write your own songs, isn't it? Yes. It's amazing, isn't it? It's amazing to be able to write your own songs, isn't it?
I can't come up with lyrics.
It's amazing that you can come up with lyrics.
I can only come up with elementary school stuff.
I understand.
I had a great time at Enoshima with Yuna.
Now I want to eat bama-ratan.
It's the only kind of song I can come up with.
You don't have a song like that?
That's all you can write, I guess.
How do you say it? Like Hugh, you know, the one with the simile.
Don't you have anything like that? Fashionably, it's difficult.
It's difficult to write about what's on your mind right now.
It's just a conversation.
That's true. It doesn't resonate with anything.
I could hit a song like, "I'm in the middle of a showroom right now.
That's interesting.
That's great.
It was fun. I got to hear New Continent.
I like Yunachii, don't you?
The other day, I was talking about how I found out that my favorite Yunichu song is "New Continent,
Then, to my surprise, I was able to hear it at a live performance right after that,
I was so happy to hear it.
It was fun to hear it.
It was great.
Happy birthday to you.
Okay, the survey is over.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. We talked quite a lot, didn't we?
That's for sure.
I could have talked about whatever I wanted to talk about,
But what? What is it?
Next, I have a list of the things I wanted to talk about in this project,
There is a list.
Uhhh...
What would you like? Ina-san.
I know it's a little late, but..,
Let's celebrate Makamanegi's birthday. Let's celebrate Makamanegi's birthday.
That's the style you say yourself.
Sorry. I'm getting this screen on someone's birthday.
Sorry.
No, no, no, because it was a month ago. Let's do it.
Please do. Then today, please give a message to Yuna Nakamura from Emma Sakura.
Yuna Nakamura message? Message? Message?
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Seventeen years old. You are a little older than Ema.
Yuna, you are always a little older than Ema.
I understand.
Dinner...
Cafe...
Whenever I wanted to go somewhere together...
I'm hungry
When he says, "I'm hungry,
I thought he wants to go somewhere with me.
That's too cute.
I can't honestly say, "Let's go out to eat.
And congratulations on turning 17.
Thank you.
You've grown up a little, haven't you?
You've grown up a little.
A little bit.
You know, you're wearing more grown-up clothes.
Really?
You're the one who's wearing a belly like that? I thought, "You're the one who's wearing clothes,
I thought, "You're wearing clothes that make you look like an adult.
And now, I would like to make a comment.
You asked me today about those clothes.
What's wrong, Yuna? I want to try on those clothes.
I told her that I wore a lot of them last year.
I didn't say anything at that time.
You look cute in that dress.
Lately, she's been saying that to me.
It made me a little nervous.I'm a little nervous about something.
Thank you very much.
And thank you for everything.
I don't know if I should say this.
I don't know if Yuna will get mad at me now,
I just suddenly felt like saying this on LINE,
I told her that I love her.
Curse you!
What do you mean?
I thought she was a real tsundere.
I just commented on it.
It says "tsundere," but I thought it was a tsundere. I just made a comment. It says "tsundere," but I thought it was a tsundere,
I think she is a tsundere.
That's exactly why I can't honestly ask her to go out to dinner.
I know Emma has her own problems, but..,
I think he's thinking about Emma, too,
But I can't say it like that,
It was a sudden line, a sudden way of saying I love you.
No, it really was. It's something you want to say all of a sudden.
People say it's because she's your sister?
Yuna is your sister?
That may be true.
Yuna says it can't be helped.
Thank you.
You're so precious, I feel like I'm going to explode.
That's for sure.
Yuna's not here.
They're not here.
Then I can wear them.
Yuna just went to the bathroom, so I'm going to tell you how I really feel now,
Oh, like that... What?
She said in a funny way, "Why did you do it like that?
But the truth is, he is always thinking about Ebitu's future, and he is also thinking about himself,
He is always thinking about the future of EBITCHU, he is always thinking about himself, he cares about us in many ways, he asks us if we are okay. He is always thinking about me and my future, and he cares about me in many ways. Thank you!
I feel better!
Did you go to the bathroom?
Yeah, I'm done. Thank you.
That's good, that's good.Good, good, good.
I feel better.
Yeah, that's good.
What are you talking about? What's the timing?
No, I mean, really, Yuna Nakamura,
I've just been talking with a fan about how Yuna Nakamura is a bit greedy, asking people to celebrate her birthday on theirs,
I was just talking with a fan about how she is a bit greedy.
Did the fans say that too?
Yes, we were talking about it.
They were talking about it. He said, "It's your birthday after all.
Sorry.
Yes, a little bit. I was just saying.
She laughed.
She laughed a lot.
I'm sure.
Because, you know, when I was out,
Emma, I think Mr. Nakamura went to the bathroom,
I was like, "What am I going to do?
Thank you very much.
That's great.
Congratulations.
Congratulations, you turned 17.
Yes, I am. So, what's next? I have something I want to do.
What?
I've already done it. Here you go.
I'm curious.
I'm not sure if Emma can make it happen, but I'm going to think about my summer plans.
Yeah!
The same one.
The same one?
Yes, the same one.
Let's think about it. This is the one where you just think about what you want to do without thinking about whether you have a job here or not, or whether it's a little expensive or not.
Is that okay? That's not right.
It's okay. Let's say whatever you want.
Wow, what shall we do?
First of all, let's have a BBQ.
I want to have a BBQ. I want to have a BBQ.
I mean, I always say I want to have a BBQ in the summer, but it never happens, does it?
No, it doesn't. It's hard to do.
It's hard to do, but I really want to barbecue.
I want to do it.
I definitely want to have a barbecue.
Yeah, yeah.
Then that's a done deal, right?
OK.
So you want to go on a short trip.
I would love to. Where do you want to go?
Well, I haven't thought about where I want to go. Sorry. But you want to go to Kyoto? Well, I didn't think about where I want to go.
Oh, I'm sorry. But I want to go to Kyoto.
In Kyoto.
You planned it well, didn't you? Right up until the last minute.
We had planned to go quite a bit, but we couldn't make it.
We couldn't go.
And then there was the pool.
Swimming pool.
I want to go to the pool.
Pool. I want to go to the pool.
I sure do.
And, and, and... I want to go to the pool. I want to go to the pool. Sure, I do.
And, you know, summer is here, right? I want to do a lot of things.
Rafting.
It's nice, isn't it?
Now that you're up there.
Bwang-bwang sounds difficult.
No, it's not. You can do it.
And I want to do it. I can't do it myself, so I want to go to the one that does it for me.
Eh, I wonder what's left.
I wonder what it is. Eh, it's something me and my fans did on our own, this year's summer vacation schedule for Ebitua.
The 30th is the Musha Shugyo live concert.
We're going to do the whole month of August as a guerrilla.
We're not going to announce where we're going to do it, but it's going to take place on an island somewhere that morning.
An island? No way, an island?
Yes, on an island, and on islands all over Japan.
I like that. That's nice.
Yes, so one day you are in Fukuoka, and the next day you are in Okinawa.
It must be tough for Yamada and the others.
Yes, the quest is tough, but what is tougher than anything else is the fans.
So, we have to guess where they are going to be tomorrow,
For example, let's say you are stepping onto an island in Tokyo.
And when you find yourself in Okinawa, you feel despair.
No, it's true.
You can't go there anymore.
I'll give them a 6:00 a.m. notice, just in case.
I see. That's a little kind of you.
If I give notice at 6:00 a.m., you can say, "Do you understand? I can say, "Yes.
Wow, that's too hard.
No way to get there.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
What is he? Summer.
You don't have to make it happen. You can say whatever you want.
Sure.
Well, I knew it.
With the water switch.
No, I'd love to.
Fireworks.
I want to do fireworks.
Let's do it.
I want to.
Let's do sunshiny fireworks, too.
Let's do sparklers.
Let's do it. Let's do it like this, just the two of us.
Let's see who can do it faster.
I'll do it. I want to do it. I want to do the exercises, too.
Why not?
I don't know.
Didn't you go? A long time ago.
I did. In the morning.
I went.
I collected stamps. Collect stamps.
That's right.
That's good.
It's at 6:30 in the morning or something.
They want me to have a yukata date.
That's what you said you wanted to do, too.
A yukata date.
It's not a date.
I want to wear a yukata with you.
I want to wear it.
That's nice.
I don't want to go on a test of courage.
Huh! Hey, hey.
Let's go to the haunted house.
I don't want to.
I don't want to go.
It's absolutely impossible, but I still don't want to go.
Yes, even now, I'm sure they go to the entrance and say, "Let's go home.
I'll definitely go in, but I'm already holding.
Let's take one more strong person with us. Like a ghost or something.
Wait a minute. I want to test my courage with the members of Ebichu.
I'd love to.
Wait, who will be the strongest?
No, first of all, Yuno is strong, right?
Yuno is the type of person who doesn't fake a gasp when she's surprised, you know?
Not Nonaka-chan?
Nonaka-chan is impossible. Because she was saying, "Oh my gosh!
Kokoro seems strong. If she comes out, I think she'll get angry.
Wait, wait, wait. Why would she come out?
I don't think so.
Either she'll get angry or she'll scream a lot.
Well, it's one or the other.
Right. And Riko seems strong.
Oh, sure.
Who is it? Who do you think?
I think Maya is weak.
But I think it's Mayamiru. But I thought it was just a false impression.
Oh, really?
I knew it.
But, I knew it...Coconacci is still a bit timid.
I mean, he can't ride the screams.
That's true.
I'm surprised he can't ride scary things like that.
Yes, that's true. Coconacci is not good at riding scary things. I can't ride the screams. That's true. I don't think there are any scary rides like that.
That's for sure.
Coconutty seems to have no reason to be afraid.
But I do feel safer when there is someone who screams more than me.
You may have that tendency.
Yes, that's true.
If it's just the two of us, I can't make them turn their backs to me,
I'd like to be able to make a group of 10 or so people do the oshikura-manju. But do you think Aya looks strong?
Certainly. Aya never makes a sound in horror games.
That's right.
She can't scream.
Oh, that's right.
I'll have Aya lead the group,
Sure.
Oh! you'd be ready for it, wouldn't you?
That's it, isn't it? She only has a great face. Very much.
It's amazing. He doesn't scream at all.
That's nice.
Okay, let me put Ayaka in the front,
M&Ms will be in the front, and then behind them, let's see,
Who is it?
Maya-san.
I don't know who Maya-san is at all.
Is he strong or weak?
I read on Maya-san that she looks strong.
Is Maya-san strong?
But you used to do that, didn't you? Ebituating Tastus.
I think I've seen it before.
Then, let's do it. Let's do a test of courage.Well, let's do some. Let's do a test of courage.
A house to test our mettle.
And then there's the flowing noodles.
I don't want to do it.
I want to do it.
I just had an idea.
It just popped into my head. It just popped into your head.
Wow, I want to do it. Soumen float.
I want to do Nagashi Somen.
And what else?
All-you-can-eat ice cream.
I want to do it.
All-you-can-eat shine mascot. Also.
All-you-can-eat donuts.
I'll never go there again. Me. Please don't participate.
Let's go with 10 donuts.
You already told them? I told everyone.
I was with my friend for the all-you-can-eat donuts.
Doughnuts are hard.
Ice cream sounds good. We're having 10 ice cream cartons right now.
I can eat them all by myself.
Doughnuts sound tough.
I couldn't even eat six.
I couldn't even eat 6 doughnuts, even though I eat a lot of Yuna.
But Nonoka got six, and I said, "Oh, Nonoka, you're full," and went back to get more.
I couldn't believe it.
I couldn't believe it. She got more than 10 pieces all by herself.
That's amazing.
Don't you want to do monja? Next time.
I think you could do monja.
Surprisingly, monja always makes me wow after I finish eating it.
I don't know what it is.
Monja is eaten before you know it.
I'd like to do that.
I want to do it.
Even making dorodang sounds fun. Even making dorodangs can be fun.
Making dorodangs.
Sure is.
Isn't that fun? The kind that makes things really shiny.
I was doing it.
I was making a swamp.
Emma Swamp?
Yeah. Emma swamp? Yeah. Emma Swamp.
You know, when they make a swamp, there's a puddle, right? That's where we put the soil.
Yes, yes.
And it gets a little bumpy.
When you pat the top, it becomes smooth, so you pour sand on it again and polish it.
So, I was making an emma swamp.
Thank you very much.
There have been swamps since before that time.
Yes.
A swamp.
It seems to be bottomless.
Bottomless, apparently.
You seem happy.
Let's do it all summer. Let's do it.
Let's do it. I want to climb mountains, too.
Let's do it as long as we can.
Let's do it. Let's do it.
I like it. It's good.
That's good.
Okay, now... How about this?
What is it?
Which one?
Father's Day project.
Pretend to be your father and read the comments.
It's difficult, isn't it? Shall we try?
Father.
Well, father, well, yes.
I'm possessed by him.
You mean you're going to possess my father?
Now that I'm here, I think I'm becoming a real father.
Well, I'm sorry. Okay, now, excuse me.
Huh?
Well, I'll let you possess it now.
I'm going to read it now, and I'm going to read it now, and I'm going to read it now.
Let's go.
I'm Papachipachi Papachipachi.
Yunachi? Yunachi is my name, not Yunachi.
Yuna's dad, right?
Ya-ya-chi-chi.
Ch-ch-ch...
Ch-ch-ch-ch-ch...
Ya-ya-chi-chi.
It's hard being a dad, isn't it?
How does it feel to have a daughter as an idol?
I don't know...
How do you feel?
I think it's great. Seeing them live.
It's unthinkable to see your own daughter on stage, isn't it? It's very emotional.
You're a good hyoyu-tei, aren't you? No, no, I am deeply emotional. That's for sure.
Well, how is my daughter, Yuna Nakamura, usually like?
Oh, what? I'm not sure about this.
Yuna?
I wonder how Yuna is.
How is she lately? Have you been seeing her? Yuna-chan.
Father Nakamura sees his daughter quite a bit, but Father doesn't see her very often,
That's right.
I don't see her often, but when I go to her live performances, I'm really moved.
What do you usually do? What do you usually eat?
Papa Chi is edamame.
Snacks?
We went out for dinner. Shabu-shabu.
That's nice.
We had shabu shabu and I ordered edamame by itself.
I asked Emma if she wanted edamame, and she said, "Oh, you want edamame. And Emma said, "Oh, you ordered edamame,
I was a little bit attracted to her, and she said, "Oh, you order edamame.
Even if it wasn't Papa Chi, I would have been surprised.
I was a little sad. It was kind of sad, wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
Even though I eat edamame often, I'm still eating this crunchy stuff.
Oh, Nakamura.
YAH, YAH Nakamura, I wonder.
What are you doing these days?
I don't know much about YAH Nakamura's normal life. No, I wonder what my father is.
I think he's eating tofu or something. Tofu? That's unusual. He's very health-conscious. He said he's been eating tofu and kimchi lately.
I like that. At my age, I start worrying about blood sugar and stuff.
So that's it.
I see.
I guess it's important.
I guess it's important to take care of your health, right?
I don't know why I'm thinking about it,
Emma.
Lately, I go to bed and go to the bedroom once.
I'm not sleeping, that's when. I'm staring at my phone, just laying there.
Then I go upstairs and come down to drink Yakult 1000.
That's the Anminna one.
That's how I sleep.
But you know what?
After dinner, he goes to his bedroom right after I come in.
He likes TikTok these days, but when he sees his daughters on TikTok, he gets all excited. Why?
Why? They started showing idols on TikTok.
Well, that's a little awkward.
It is for me.
Let's just get this over with.
Oh, my God, are you okay?
Is everything okay?
I thought you just stopped for a second.
Are you okay? Are you okay? I just felt like it stopped for a second.
Are you okay?
Is everything okay?
Well, let's go to the ending.
Let's go.
What kind of tension am I supposed to be in?
The 70th edition of Ebichu's Delightful and Irrelevant Showroom came to an ending in no time. The 70th edition of the delightful and unfunny showroom in Ebichu came to an ending in no time.
We did it. It's early.
It's early, isn't it? It was over in the blink of an eye while I had you tell me today. It's over, isn't it? That was quick. It's over in the blink of an eye while you had me say it today.
So, I would like to make an announcement here from Ebichu.
Here it is.
The EBCHU Summer Family Eisaku, or Famiain Yamanakako 2024 for short, will be held on August 17 and 18 at Lake Yamanakako.
will be held on August 17 and 18 at Kirara Theater Hibiki, Lake Yamanakako Koryu Plaza.
Yay!
I love it. Famian.
Very excited.
Please come.
And then, and then. Sakura Emma's birthday solo live, Honey Emile Numa 2, will be held on September 5th, the day of her birthday, at KTV Zesshin Yokohama,
I'm sure you will see a slightly different Sakura Ema from last year,
Please come and join us. I'm looking forward to seeing you.
Please come.
Please come, Mr. Nakamura.
I will be there. I will bash again this year.
Thank you very much.
Yes, I will. You will also appear at the Lucky Fest. I'll be there. I will bash again this year. Thank you very much.
I will also be appearing at Lucky Fest, and I will be performing at TIFF with my sister Shiritsue and sister Shiritsue.
I am looking forward to it.
I want to make a mysterious decoration for this.
There will be an event on August 4, the anniversary of our formation, at a certain place in Tokyo.
I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to it. Please wait for further information.
And then there is the center.
It's the first time.
The center, Emayuna.
There is a central on October 5.
How will it be?
I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to it.
Familiar.
We are looking forward to seeing you all.
We are waiting for you.
Yes, I'm looking forward to it. We're looking forward to seeing you. We're waiting for you. And now, let's check out the final top 5 ranking.
I wonder who they are.
Oh, they're here.
They're here.
Well, let's go. Okay, here we go.
Fifth place, Mr. ON. Thank you very much.
Fourth place, Mr. TOMOKI. Thank you very much.
3rd, MAYUKI-san. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
I am very happy.
I'm very happy. Thank you very much. Thank you very much. I'm glad.
I'm glad. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Yes, so, with shrimpy delight,
Oh, let's talk some more.
Yes, I know.
We're in the front, we've been here 70 times, we have to talk a little more.
I have to talk.
I'm still a little bit possessed by my father.
I can't get rid of it.
I'm halfway there.
Half of it has come out. I said, "Let's talk.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
What do you want to talk about? Something you want to talk about.
Oh, sure.
How was it?
Me?
I am,
I said it's been a while.
Yuna-san, it's been about a year. How was it? I thought that being an MC is a tough but rewarding job.
It was very easy to do.
Thank you very much.
Did you enjoy it? The showroom with Mr. Sakurayama.
It was fun. I have never done a showroom with Mr. Sakurayama,
I've only done it with Mr. Sakurayama, so it's always easy to do.
It was great.
I'm glad I got to talk to you.
I'm glad. That's great.
It says serious. It says "serious.
You say it's serious.
Yeah.
Hey, they don't do it at all.
That's the veteran Yuna.
A veteran?
Yeah.
She said it's a hero interview.
That's right. Thank you very much.
The story of Emachi's long line that came on the day of his birthday.
That's right.
I sent him a long line.
Let's do it again sometime near Mr. Sakurayama's birthday.
Send it to me.
I'll send it.
So, that's the end of the 70th edition of EBICHU's funny and funny showroom.
Sad. It's too soon.
Every time I visit the showroom, it seems to go faster.
We'll let you know when the next installment is coming.
That's all for now, Shiri-chan Ebi7gaku.
Bye bye.
This is Emayuna.
Bye bye bye. It was bye bye bye you you you